<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arsenal Players</string>

    <string name="players_name">Players Name</string>
    <string name="description">Player Profile</string>

    <string name="list">List</string>
    <string name="grid">Grid</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="arsenal_players">Arsenal Players</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>

    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Aaron Ramsdale</item>
        <item>Matthew Charles Turner</item>
        <item>Benjamin William White</item>
        <item>Gabriel Megalhaes</item>
        <item>Takehiro Tomiyasu</item>
        <item>Oleksandr Zinchenko</item>
        <item>Thomas Partey</item>
        <item>Martin Odegaard</item>
        <item>Mohamed Elneny</item>
        <item>Granit Xhaka</item>
        <item>Gabriel Jesus</item>
        <item>Gabriel Martinelli</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_description" align="justify">
        <item>Aaron Ramsdale (Aaron Christopher Ramsdale) is a goalkeeper currently playing for Arsenal. He wears the squad number 1 and was born on May 14, 1998 in Stoke-on-Trent. Ramsdale made his debut for Arsenal on August 25, 2021 in a League Cup match against West Bromwich Albion, which Arsenal won 6-0. Prior to joining Arsenal, Ramsdale played for Bournemouth, and had loan spells at Chesterfield and AFC Wimbledon. He also played for Sheffield United before moving to Arsenal. If you want to follow him on Twitter, his handle is @AaronRamsdale98.\n\nTalented young goalkeeper Aaron joined in the summer, having been part of the England squad that reached the final of Euro 2020. Very highly regarded throughout the early part of his career, Aaron made the switch from Sheffield United – the club at which he started his pro career – making his debut aged 18 in 2016.\n\nHe joined Bournemouth in 2017, and enjoyed loan spells at Chesterfield and AFC Wimbledon – winning Young Player of the Year award at the latter, and helping them survive relegation from League One.\n\nA regular for England at youth levels from under-18 to under-21, the right-footed stopper won the UEFA U19 Championships in 2017, keeping three clean sheets in his five appearances, then played 15 times for the Under-21s.</item>
        <item>Matthew Charles Turner (Matt Turner) is Arsenal\'s second goalkeeper. He wears the squad number 30 and was born on June 24, 1994 in New Jersey, USA. Turner is also a member of the USA national team. Prior to his current club, Turner played for Jersey Express and New England Revolution, and had a loan spell at Richmond Kickers. If you want to follow him on Twitter, his handle is @headdturnerr.\n\nUSA international goalkeeper Matt joined in the summer, having played all his football in America until that point. A regular for New England Revolution from 2018, he had previously been loaned to Richmond Kickers after joining from Jersey Express.\n\nLater that year he played every game as USA won the CONCACAF Gold Cup, keeping five clean sheets in the tournament, earning the Golden Glove award. He was also named MLS Goalkeeper of the Year in 2021, and he saved two penalties in the MLS All-Star Game later that year. An Arsenal fan since his childhood, he has dual American-Lithuanian nationality due to his parents.</item>
        <item>Ben White (Benjamin William White) is a defender who currently plays for Arsenal. He wears the squad number 4 and was born on October 8, 1997 in Poole. White is also a member of the England national team. His debut for Arsenal was on August 13, 2021, in a Premier League match against Brentford, which Arsenal lost 2-0. Prior to joining Arsenal, White played for Brighton and Hove Albion, and had loan spells at Newport County, Peterborough United, and Leeds United.\n\nA big-money signing in the summer, central defender Ben has gone from strength to strength in recent seasons.\n\nHe returned to Brighton last season, winning their Player of the Year award, and capped the season by making his England debut against Austria on June 2, 2021. He was later named in the Euro 2020 squad, though did not feature. A ball-playing centre back with great distribution, he can also play as a defensive midfielder or at right back.</item>
        <item>Gabriel Magalhaes is a Brazilian football player who currently serves as a defender for Arsenal. He was born on December 19, 1997, in Sao Paulo, Brazil. Gabriel wears squad number 6 for Arsenal and has represented Brazil at the national level.\n\nGabriel made his debut for Arsenal against Fulham in the Premier League on September 12, 2020, in a 3-0 victory. He scored his first goal for Arsenal in the same match against Fulham. Prior to joining Arsenal, Gabriel played for Avai, Lille, Troyes on loan, and Dinamo Zagreb on loan.\n\nGabriel slotted seamlessly into the Gunners defence during his first season in London, impressing with his combativeness and composure in the back line, and contributing some important goals too.\n\nHe played for his country at the 2017 South American U-20 Championships, and was part of the Under-23 squad at the summer Olympics in Tokyo.</item>
        <item>Takehiro Tomiyasu is a Japanese football player who currently plays as a defender for Arsenal.He was born on November 5, 1998, in Fukuoka, Japan. Tomiyasu wears squad number 18 for Arsenal and has represented Japan at the international level. Tomiyasu made his debut for Arsenal in a Premier League match against Norwich City on September 11, 2021, which Arsenal won 1-0. Before joining Arsenal, Tomiyasu played for Avispa Fukuoka, Sint-Truiden, and Bologna.\n\nThe powerful Japanese right back, who can also play at centre back, began his career with Avispa Fukuoka in his home country before moving to Europe in January 2018. He spent 18 months at Belgian club Sint-Truiden, where he was voted the club’s Player of the Season for the 2018/19 campaign, before his performances earned him a move to Italy in July 2019.\n\nTakehiro then became a regular in Bologna’s defence, making 63 appearances in his two seasons there. Known as Tomi, he is noted for his composure and technical ability, and is a regular Japan international, featuring at the 2020 summer Olympics in his home country.</item>
        <item>Oleksandr Zinchenko is a defender for arsenal player. He was born on December 15, 1996, in Radomyshi, Ukraine. Zinchenko wears squad number 35 for Manchester City and has represented Ukraine at the international level. Before joining Arsenal, Zinchenko played for Ufa, Manchester City, PSV (loan).\n\nA childhood Arsenal supporter, Oleksandr joined from Manchester City in July, reuniting with Mikel Arteta, who had coached him at City.\n\nThe Ukraine international won four Premier League titles with his former club, as well as four League Cups, one FA Cup and played the full 90 minutes of the 2021 Champions League final.\n\nComfortable playing at left back or in midfield, Alex – as he is known by team-mates – became the youngest ever goalscorer for the Ukraine national team when he netted against Romania in May 2016, aged 19. He was named Ukraine Footballer of the Year in 2019 and went on to become his country\'s youngest captain, taking the arm band aged 24, against France in March 2021.</item>
        <item>Thomas Partey is a Ghanaian football player who plays as a midfielder for Arsenal. He was born on June 13, 1993, in Krobo Odumase, Ghana. Partey wears squad number 5 for Arsenal and has represented Ghana at the international level. Partey made his debut for Arsenal in a Premier League match against Manchester City on October 17, 2020, in which Arsenal lost 0-1. Before joining Arsenal, Partey played for Atletico Madrid, Mallorca on loan, and Almeria on loan.\n\nA powerful, skilful central midfielder, Thomas gave a number of stand-out performances during his debut season.\n\nSoon after arriving from Atletico Madrid just before the transfer deadline, the Ghanaian was making his mark in the Premier League – being named Man of the Match in the 1-0 win at Old Trafford.\n\nA combative ball-winner with the ability to dominate games, Thomas lifted the Europa League and European Super Cup, and also played in the 2016 Champions League final for his previous club. During five stellar seasons in the Spanish capital, he earned a reputation as one of the league\’s outstanding players.</item>
        <item>Martin Odegaard is a Norwegian football player who currently plays as a midfielder for Arsenal. He was born on December 17, 1998, in Drammen, Norway. Odegaard wears squad number 8 for Arsenal and has represented Norway at the international level. Odegaard made his debut for Arsenal in a Premier League match against Manchester United on January 30, 2021, in a 0-0 draw. He scored his first goal for Arsenal in a Europa League match against Olympiacos on March 11, 2021, in a 3-1 victory.\n\nHaving enjoyed a highly-productive loan spell with us in the second half of last season, Martin made his switch from Real Madrid permanent in the summer.\n\nA highly creative, technical attacking midfielder, Martin is most comfortable in the No. 10 role but can also play in deeper central midfield or out wide. Something of a child prodigy, the Norway international made his senior debut for Stromgodset aged 15, then signed for Madrid shortly afterwards and became their youngest-ever player, making his debut aged 16 years and 157 days.\n\nHe enjoyed three successful loan spells in Holland and Spain before playing for the Gunners last season, and scoring in the north London derby victory at the Emirates in March. He has been a full international since August 2014, when he became his country\’s youngest-ever player, aged 15 years and 253 days.</item>
        <item>Mohamed Elneny is an Egyptian football player who plays as a midfielder for Arsenal. He was born on July 11, 1992, in El-Mahalla El-Kubra, Egypt. Elneny wears squad number 25 for Arsenal. Elneny made his debut for Arsenal in an FA Cup match against Burnley on January 30, 2016, in a 2-1 victory. He scored his first goal for Arsenal in a Champions League match against Barcelona on March 16, 2016, in a 3-1 loss.\n\nIt was another impressive season for Mo, during which the Egypt international passed the 100-appearance mark for the club.He impressed with his usual industry and intelligence in central midfield, while also chipping in with some spectacular goals. In December he blasted home from long-range in the Europa League group stage win at Dundalk – a strike later voted Arsenal.com Goal of the Season.\n\nMo also netted against Olympiacos before registering his first Premier League goal, away to Newcastle United in May.\n\nNow into his seventh season with the Gunners, he joined from Basel, where he won four consecutive Swiss league titles. A full international since 2011, he scored in the 2017 Africa Cup of Nations final, but Egypt lost 2-1 to Cameroon.</item>
        <item>Granit Xhaka is a Swiss football player who plays as a midfielder for Arsenal. He was born on September 27, 1992, in Basel, Switzerland. Xhaka wears squad number 34 for Arsenal and has represented Switzerland at the international level. Xhaka made his debut for Arsenal in a Premier League match against Liverpool on August 14, 2016, in a 4-3 loss. He scored his first goal for Arsenal in a Premier League match against Hull City on September 17, 2016, in a 4-1 victory.\n\nCombative midfielder Granit remains a cornerstone of the Arsenal midfield after another productive season in 2020/21 during which he featured 45 times.\n\nThe Switzerland international began his career at Basel, where he won two league titles and the Swiss Cup before joining Borussia Monchengladbach and making 140 appearances across four years for the Bundesliga side.\n\nSince joining the Gunners in 2016 he has lifted four more trophies, winning both the FA Cup and Community Shield twice. The midfielder, who is tough in the tackle and boasts a fearsome long-range shot, has represented his country at two World Cups and two European Championships, most recently at Euro 2020, where he was outstanding in the quarter-final win over France on penalties.</item>
        <item>Gabriel Jesus is a Brazilian football player who plays as a forward for Arsenal. He was born on April 3, 1997, in Sao Paulo, Brazil. Jesus wears squad number 9 for Arsenal. Jesus started his career at Palmeiras before moving to Manchester City in 2017. He joined Arsenal on loan in January 2022 and has been a key player for the team since his arrival. Off the pitch, Jesus is active on social media and has a Twitter account with the handle @gabrieljesus9.\n\nA dynamic forward with a wealth of Premier League experience, Gabriel joined in the summer to reunite with Mikel Arteta, who had coached him at previous club Manchester City.\n\nThe striker, who can also play in a deeper role or on the flank, won four Premier League titles during a glittering five-and-a-half-year career with City, as well as one FA Cup, three League Cups and he played in the 2020/21 Champions League final.\n\nIn total he scored 95 goals for the club, but was also known for his creativity – he led the way for Premier League assists for them last term with eight, to go with his eight goals in the league.A teenage sensation at first club Palmeiras, he made his first-team debut as a 17 year old and was soon earning international recognition.</item>
        <item>Gabriel Martinelli is a Brazilian footballer who plays as a forward for Arsenal, wearing the squad number 11. He was born on June 18, 2001 in Guarulhos, Brazil. Martinelli made his Arsenal debut in a Premier League match against Newcastle United on August 11, 2019, which Arsenal won 1-0. He scored his first goal for the club in a Carabao Cup match against Nottingham Forest on September 24, 2019, helping Arsenal secure a 5-0 victory. Prior to joining Arsenal, Martinelli played for Ituano.\n\nOne of the most exciting players of his generation, Gabriel once again highlighted his vast potential last season. An electric forward – whether operating as a striker or wide on the left – the Brazilian returned from a knee injury in December and picked up where he left off.\n\nAn excellent finisher with an indefatigable work ethic, \‘Gabi\’ (full name Gabriel Teodoro Martinelli Silva) scored in our Premier League wins at Sheffield United and Crystal Palace.\n\nThis is his third season at the club, after bursting on to the scene in 2019/20 following his arrival from Brazilian side Ituano. A Brazil youth international capped at under-23 level, the highlight of his debut season in England was a magnificent solo goal in a 2-2 Premier League draw away to Chelsea, winning the Arsenal.com Goal of the Season award.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/aaron_ramsdale</item>
        <item>@drawable/mat_turner</item>
        <item>@drawable/ben_white</item>
        <item>@drawable/gabriel_magalhaes</item>
        <item>@drawable/takehiro_tomiyasu</item>
        <item>@drawable/oleksandr_zinchenko</item>
        <item>@drawable/thomas_partey</item>
        <item>@drawable/martin_odegaard</item>
        <item>@drawable/mohamed_elneny</item>
        <item>@drawable/granit_xhaka</item>
        <item>@drawable/gabriel_jesus</item>
        <item>@drawable/gabriel_martinelli</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>